Guide to the Rand School of Social Science Records TAM.007
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Publications, 1906-1955
  - Subseries VID: Index to Labor Articles, 1926- 1953
    - Index to Labor Articles, v. 27, no. 7-8/9-10 (combined issue), Jul 1953-Oct 1953 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Subseries VIE: Serials, 1918-1955
    The serials part of the publications series contains nine short lived internal publications. The most prominent serial publications in this part include the Institute of Social Studies Bulletin(XIII:F:5:1), The Labor student(XIII:8:5:3), The Rand School News(XIII:F:5:7), Russian Affairs(before it was incorporated into the New Leader;XIII:F:5:8), and The Student Worker(XIII:F:5:9). The serials are arranged in alphabetical order according to the title of the publication. Separate issues within a particular serial are arranged in chronological order. A full bibliographical citation for each serial can be found in the complete reel list for this collection.
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 1, Feb 1951 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:1
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 2, May 1951 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 3, Oct 1951 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 4, Jan 1952 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 5, Spring 1952 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 6, Summer 1952 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 7, Fall 1952 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 1, no. 8, Winter 1952 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 1, Spring 1953 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 2, Summer 1953 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 3, Fall 1953 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 4, Winter 1953 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 5, Spring 1954 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 6, Summer 1954 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 7, Fall 1954 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 2, no. 8, Winter 1954 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 3, no. 1, Spring 1955 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 3, no. 2, Summer 1955 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Institute of Social Studies, v. 3, no. 3, Fall 1955 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin: Womens Committee of the Rand School of Social Science, v. 1, no. 2, Jan 1934 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:2
    - Bulletin: Womens Committee of the Rand School of Social Science, v. 1, no. 3, Feb 1934 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Bulletin: Womens Committee of the Rand School of Social Science, v. 1, no. 4, Mar 1934 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 1, Jan 1925 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:3
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 2, Feb 1925 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 3-4, Mar 1925-Apr 1925 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 4, Aug 1925 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 5, Jun 1926-Jul 1926 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 6, Dec 1926 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Labor Student, v. 1, no. 7, Jun 1927 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - The Rand Rambler, v. 1, no. 1, Nov 1929 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:4
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. [1], Oct 1937 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:5
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 2, Nov 1937 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 3, Dec 1937 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 4 (lacks v. 1, no. 4), Jan 1938 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 5, Feb 1938 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 6, Mar 1938 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Rand School Advance, v. 1, no. 6 [sic], Apr 1938 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Rand School Fellowship Bulletin, v. 1, no. 1, Mar 14, 1925 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      Film R-7124, Reel 53: Frame XIII:F:5:6
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 1, ca.Feb 19, 1918 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:5:7
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 2, Mar 1918 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 3, May 1918 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 4, Jun 1918 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 5, Nov 1918 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 1, no. 6, Dec 1918 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 2, no. 2, Feb 1919 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 2, no. 3, Apr 1919 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 2, no. 4, Jun 1919 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 3, no. 1, Sep 1919 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News, v. 3, no. 2, Jan 1920 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 1, Sep 1920 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 2, Oct 1920 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 3, Nov 1920 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 4, Dec 1920 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 5, Jan 1921 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 6, Feb 1921 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 1, no. 7, Mar 1921 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 1, Sep 1921 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 2, Oct 1921-Nov 1921 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 3, Dec 1921 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 4, Jan 1922-Feb 1922 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 5, Mar 1922 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 6, Oct 1922 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 7, Nov 1922 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 8, Dec 1922 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 2, no. 8A, Dec 1922 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 1, Jun 1923 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 2, Sep 1923 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 3, Oct 1923 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 3, no. 4, Dec 1923 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 4, no. 1, Aug 1924 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 4, no. 2, Sep 1924 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 4, no. 3, Oct 1924-Nov 1924 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. (?), no. 1, Nov 1934 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 1, Sep 1939 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 1 [sic], Oct 1939 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 2, Nov 1939 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Rand School News and Book Review, v. 5, no. 3, Dec 1939 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 1, Oct 1944 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:5:8
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 2, Nov 1944 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 3, Dec 1944 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 4, Jan 1945 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 5, Mar 1945 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 6, Apr 1945 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 7, May 1945 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 8, Jul 1945 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Russian Affairs, v. 1 no. 9, Oct 1945 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 1, Jan 6, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:5:9
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 2, Jan 18, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 3, Jan 27, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 4, Feb 1, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 5, Feb 8, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 6, Feb 15, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 7, Feb 24, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 8, Mar 2, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 9, Mar 9, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 10, Mar 16, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 11, Mar 23, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 12, Mar 30, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 13, Apr 6, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 14, Apr 13, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 2, no. 1, Sep 23, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 3, no. 1, Sep 26, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 2, no. 5, Oct 10, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 2, no. 6, Oct 17, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 2, Feb 1, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 3, Feb 8, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 4, Feb 21, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 5, Feb 28, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Student Worker, v. 1, no. 5 [sic], Mar 14, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Subseries VIF: Course Bulletins and Announcements, 1906-1955
    The course bulletins and announcements part of the publications series consists of 155 items. These bulletins pertain to the general course curriculum of the Rand School from 1906 to 1955, and to such special education programs as the Trade Union Institute, the Physical Education Department, summer school, the Workers' Training Course, correspondence courses, Rand High School, Alertness Courses, Political Training Courses, the Newark School of Social Science, the Rand School of Northern New Jersey, and the Trade Union Leadership Training Program. The items in this part are arranged in chronological order. A full bibliographical citation for each item in this part is located in the complete reel list for this collection.
    - Rand School Prospectus, Jul 15, 1906 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:1
    - First Year Bulletin for First Term, Oct 1, 1906-Dec 23, 1906 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:2
    - Second Year Bulletin for First Term, Sep 30, 1907-Dec 22, 1907 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:3
    - Third Year Bulletin for First Term, Sep 28, 1908-Dec 20, 1908 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:4
    - Third Year Bulletin for Second Term, Jan 10, 1909-Apr 30, 1909 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:5
    - Fourth Year Bulletin for Second Term, Jan 7, 1910-Apr 28, 1910 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:6
    - Fifth Year Bulletin for Second Term, Jan 3, 1911-Apr 2, 1911 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:7
    - Sixth Year Bulletin for First Term, Oct 11, 1911-Jan 19, 1912 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:8
    - Announcement of Courses, 1911-1912 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:9
    - Sixth Year Supplementary Bulletin, Dec 5, 1911-Jun 7, 1912 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:10
    - Announcement of Courses, 1912-1913 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:11
    - Seventh Year Courses, 1912-1913 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:12
    - Full-Time Courses, 1913-1914 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:13
    - Courses of Study, 1913-1914 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:14
    - Bulletin, 1915-1916 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:15
    - Bulletin, 1916-1917 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:16
    - Bulletin, 1918-1919 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:19
    - Bulletin, 1917-1918 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:17
    - Summer Season of The Rand School, 1918 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:18
    - Announcement of the Correspondence Department, 1919 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:20
    - Summer Season of The Rand School, Jul 7, 1919-Aug 16, 1919 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:21
    - Summer Season of The Rand School, Jul 7, 1919-Aug 16, 1919 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:22
    - Workers Training Course, undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:23
    - Bulletin, 1919-1920 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:24
    - Third Summer Session, 1920 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:25
    - Bulletin, 1920-1921 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:26
    - Announcement of the Correspondence Department, 1920 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:27
    - Physical Education Department, 1921-1922 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:28
    - Bulletin, 1922-1923 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:29
    - Full-Time Training Course, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:30
    - Summer Session, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:31
    - Physical Education Department, 1923-1924 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:32
    - Physical Education Department, 1924-1925 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:33
    - Courses Now Beginning, 1925-1926 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:34
    - Physical Education Department Announcement, 1925-1926 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:35
    - Preliminary Announcement for Courses for Trade Unionists, May 1926 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:36
    - Schedule of Courses, 1927-1928 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:37
    - New Courses, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:38
    - New Courses, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:39
    - New Courses, 1927 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:40
    - Schedule for Second Term, 1927-1928 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:41
    - Preliminary Announcement, 1928-1929 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:42
    - Announcement, 1928-1929 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:43
    - Mid-Winter Bulletin, Jan 1929 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:44
    - Twenty-Fourth Season, 1929-1930 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:45
    - Winter-Spring Twenty-Fourth Season, 1930 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:46
    - Evening Courses and Lectures: Twenty-Fifth Season, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:47
    - Evening Courses and Lectures: Twenty-Fifth Season, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:48
    - Winter Courses, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:49
    - Preliminary Announcement, 1931-1932 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:50
    - Evening Courses and Lectures, 1931-1932 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:51
    - Winter Courses and Lectures, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:52
    - 1932-1933 Classes (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:53
    - Correspondence Course: Introduction to Scientific Socialism, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:54
    - Among the Courses and Lectures, Nov 14, 1932-Dec 23, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:55
    - Courses and Lectures, Jan 9, 1933-Apr 7, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:56
    - Evening Classes and Lectures, 1933-1934 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:57
    - Correspondence Courses: I. Introduction to Socialism II. Elements of Economics, 1933-1934 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:58
    - Mid-Winter Bulletin, Jan 1934-Mar 1934 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:59
    - Evening Classes and Lectures, 1934-1935 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:60
    - Correspondence Courses. I. Intro­duction to Socialism. II. Trade Unionism in Theory and Practice, 1934-1935 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:61
    - Mid-Winter Bulletin, Jan 1935 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:62
    - Spring Term 1935, Mar 20, 1935-Apr 25, 1935 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:63
    - Thirty Years, 1935-1936 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:64
    - The Rand School Expects You, 1935 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:65
    - Rand High School, 1935-1936 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:66
    - Mid-Winter Bulletin, Jan 1936 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:67
    - Fall Term, 1936-1937 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:68
    - Fall Term Lectures, 1936-1937 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:69
    - An Educational Program for Winter-Spring, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:70
    - Fall Term, 1937-1938 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:71
    - Announcing the Opening of The Newark School, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:72
    - Winter Term, 1938 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:73
    - Trade Union Institute, 1938 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:74
    - Alertness Courses, Jan 1938 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:75
    - Fall Term, 1938 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:76
    - Political Training Courses: Fall Term, 1938 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:77
    - Trade Union Training Course, 1938 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:78
    - Newark School Calendar, 1938-1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:79
    - Winter Term Bulletin, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:80
    - Alertness Course: Spring Term, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:81
    - Courses for Group Leaders, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:82
    - Political Training Course, Jan 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:83
    - Courses for Social Workers: Spring Term, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:84
    - Training Courses for Trade Unionists: Winter Term, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:85
    - Fall Bulletin, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:86
    - Alertness Courses: Fall, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:87
    - Training Courses for Trade Unionists: Fall, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:88
    - Announcement of Courses: Winter Term, Jan 15, 1940-Apr 18, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:89
    - Alertness Courses: Spring Term, Feb 5, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:90
    - Training Courses for Leaders of Youth Groups, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:91
    - A Training Program for Social Case Workers in Public Assistance: Winter, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:92
    - Newark School Bulletin of Classes, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:93
    - Fall Term: Announcement of Classes, Sep 16, 1940-Dec 19, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:94
    - Alertness Courses: Fall Term, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:95
    - A Training Program for Social Case Workers in Public Assistance: Fall, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:96
    - Youth Education Institute, Sep 1940 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:97
    - Newark School Calendar: First Term, 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:98
    - Announcement of Courses: Spring Term, Jan 13, 1941-Apr 17, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:99
    - Alertness Courses: Spring Term, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:100
    - Fall Term Bulletin, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:101
    - CPA Examination Review Courses, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:102
    - Program: Fall Dinner, Newark School, 1941 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:103
    - Winter Term Bulletin, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:104
    - Fall Term Bulletin, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:105
    - What Every intelligent Worker Should Know, 1942 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:106
    - Fall Term Bulletin, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:107
    - Winter Term Prospectus, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:108
    - Trade Union Training Courses prospectus: Winter, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:109
    - Trade Union Training Courses Bulletin: Winter, Jan 1944 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:110
    - Bulletin G: Spring Term, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:111
    - General Bulletin: Fall Term, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:112
    - Institute for Russian Studies: Fall Term, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:113
    - General Bulletin: Spring Term, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:114
    - Trade Union Training Courses and Labor Seminar: Fall-Spring, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:115
    - General Bulletin: Fall Term, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:116
    - Trade Union Training Courses: Fall Term, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:117
    - General Bulletin: Spring Term, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:118
    - Bulletin: Fall, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:119
    - Bulletin: Spring Term, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      Film R-7124, Reel 54: Frame XIII:F:6:120